[{"answer": "Do I have to be looking for something", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You can pretty much tell what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What do you think I'm looking for", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I strongly doubt if you could fix me up. In that department", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " I been seeing it coming for a long time, Kid. Long time", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, you ain't been hiding it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, you ain't been hiding it", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Sure, you got to know. We all got to know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well I got to know", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Sometime or other we got to find out how much juice we got", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't figure to take him right away. But if I can hang in there long enough, I can outlast him. If I can outlast him, I got a chance. You admit that, don't you, that I got a chance", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Did you think you were ready when you sat down with Whistling my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Turkish Bath. After we're through shopping. I'm treating you, my friend", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You don't do anything. That's what's so marvelous. They do it to you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I slept okay", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No I don't mind", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Why?  What's the matter", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Thought what", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That would be fine, Kid. Just fine", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There's no reason for not going right now unless", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Unless you wanted to go to bed first", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "U", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Coffee", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Neither do I", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Promise", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, that's it, then. Monday night, my friend at the Dorset Hotel. And may the best man win", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah, he's going to give you trouble", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Play what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Same deck is good enough", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Alright, alright", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " It's", "docId": "Cincinnati-Kid_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " If I go, I'm not going back to the apartment. If I go", "qsentId": 36}]